[{"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Piers"]}, "docId": "121025pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NN", ",", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 35, "question": "Senator, how are you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 36, "answer": "Fine, Piers.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Colin Powell", "Barack Obama"]}, "docId": "121025pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "VBG", "NN", "DT", "VBG", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "NN", "NNP", "NNP", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 37, "question": "How are you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 38, "answer": "You've been spitting blood all morning about Colin Powell endorsing Barack Obama again.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121025pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "JJ", "IN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 39, "question": "Why are you so angry about it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "RB", "JJ", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 40, "answer": "I'm not angry about it.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121025pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "NN", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 47, "question": "Is that dignified for the president of the United States to use that term about his rival?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "IN", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NNPS", "TO", "VB", "IN", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 48, "answer": "Of course not.", "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["United States"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121025pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 59, "question": "Could in the end Wisconsin potentially be more important than Ohio here?", "question_pos_tagged": ["MD", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NNP", "RB", "VB", "RBR", "JJ", "IN", "NNP", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 60, "answer": "I think it could be.", "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Wisconsin", "Ohio"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Bashar Assad"], "LOCATION": ["Syria"]}, "docId": "121025pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "JJ", "TO", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "CC", "RB", ",", "IN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "EX", "VBP", "JJ", "JJ", "NNS", "IN", "NNP", "RB", "WDT", "VBP", "VBG", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "VBG", "IN", "NNS", "WDT", "VBP", "VBG", "IN", "TO", "NNS", "WP", "VBP", "JJ", "RB", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "JJ", "PRP", "VBZ", "."], "qSentId": 73, "question": "What do you make of it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 74, "answer": "Well, it will be interesting to see whether it holds or not, because, you know, there are many disparate groups in Syria now that are fighting against Bashar Assad ranging from jihadists which are pouring in to people who are pro-democracy so I'm not sure it holds.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121025pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "IN", "DT", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 91, "question": "But without that original posting, then the e-mail at the center of your complaint becomes obsolete, doesn't it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ",", "RB", "DT", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "VBZ", "JJ", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 92, "answer": "Well, I think -- I think you have to look at this in its entirety.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121025pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "."], "qSentId": 113, "question": "Were you involved in all three of the president's debates this time?", "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "DT", "CD", "IN", "DT", "NN", "POS", "NNS", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 114, "answer": "I was.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Obama", "Romney"]}, "docId": "121025pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "NNP", "NNP", "VBD", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "VBD", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "CC", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "IN", "IN", "."], "qSentId": 117, "question": "So what the hell happened on that first one?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "WP", "DT", "NN", "VBD", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "CD", "."], "aSentId": 118, "answer": "Well, President Obama said that Governor Romney had a good night and he didn't, and I have to leave it at that.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121025pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "IN", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 124, "question": "You go along with that or not?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "IN", "IN", "DT", "CC", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 125, "answer": "No, I don't go with that.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121025pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "qSentId": 134, "question": "What is your gut feeling about exactly where we are right now?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "PRP$", "NN", "VBG", "IN", "RB", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 135, "answer": "Sure.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121025pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["EX", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 145, "question": "What is your view?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 146, "answer": "There is no panic.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Mr. Romney", "Romney"]}, "docId": "121025pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "RB", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "CC", "PRP$", "NN", "VBP", "NNS", "TO", "DT", "NN", "RB", "RB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "CC", "IN", "JJ", "JJ", "NNS", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "IN", ",", "IN", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBN", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 175, "question": "What do you say to that?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "TO", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 176, "answer": "Well, apparently Mr. Romney, Governor Romney, and his attorney are strangers to the truth not only with that comment but with many other comments they've made during this campaign, because, of course, I've not shopped them at all.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121025pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "WP", "NNS", ",", "RB", ",", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 181, "question": "So I asked Governor Romney, how low can you stoop, Governor Romney, to allow your attorney to launch this attack on a single mom who you know cannot defend herself because she is still under that gag order?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBD", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "WRB", "JJ", "NN", "PRP", "VB", ",", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "TO", "VB", "PRP$", "NN", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "WP", "PRP", "VBP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "PRP", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 182, "answer": "Well, we'll see what happens, obviously, with the legal action here.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121025pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "PRP", "CC", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", ",", "IN", "EX", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 190, "question": "Does this stagger you that these politicians running for the Senate, second one now, would say such extraordinary things about something as sensitive as rape and abortion and so on?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "DT", "NN", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "VBG", "IN", "DT", "NNP", ",", "JJ", "CD", "RB", ",", "MD", "VB", "JJ", "JJ", "NNS", "IN", "NN", "IN", "JJ", "IN", "NN", "CC", "NN", "CC", "RB", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 191, "answer": "Well, I wish I could say that it surprises me but it doesn't, because there is that kind of extremism in the Republican Party.", "question_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Senate"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121025pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "RB", "VB", "PRP$", "NN", "TO", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "PRP", "VBZ", "."], "qSentId": 202, "question": "Do you have a respect for people who perhaps don't phrase it such a clumsy way but have a religious conviction about the sanctity of life in any kind of situation like that?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "WP", "RB", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "PRP", "JJ", "DT", "NN", "NN", "CC", "VBP", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 203, "answer": "Well, I definitely support his right to have any religious conviction he wants.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121025pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "JJ", "IN", "DT", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "CC", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 233, "question": "When you see the sexualization of the polling booth, as a woman, do you feel comfortable with that?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", ",", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 234, "answer": "Well, first of all, I don't have a horse in the ring or dog in the fight because I'm Canadian.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121025pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "IN", "NN", "VBZ", "VBN", "."], "qSentId": 256, "question": "But what is more offensive, him doing that or him continuing to support a candidate for the Senate who thinks it's God's intent for women to be raped and impregnated?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "WP", "VBZ", "RBR", "JJ", ",", "PRP", "VBG", "IN", "CC", "PRP", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "WP", "VBZ", "PRP", "VBZ", "NNP", "POS", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "TO", "VB", "VBN", "CC", "VBN", "."], "aSentId": 257, "answer": "No, that man has apologized.", "question_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Senate"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121025pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "VBN", "IN", "WP", "PRP", "VBD", "."], "qSentId": 269, "question": "But that -- do you think he's right?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "DT", ":", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 270, "answer": "He hasn't apologized for what he said.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERCENT": ["56 percent"]}, "docId": "121025pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "WP", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "TO", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "IN", "CD", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "VBP", "NNS", "CC", "RB", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "NN", "WDT", "NN", "VBZ", "VBG", "IN", ",", "WDT", "VBZ", "PRP$", "JJ", ",", "IN", "NN", "WDT", "VBN", "``", "NNS", ".", "''"], "qSentId": 281, "question": "But Marjorie Clifton, what do you think?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 282, "answer": "Well, I think what this ad speaks to is the fact that 56 percent of voters are women and specifically in this independent swing vote that everybody is clamoring for, that is your demographic, that woman that created \"Girls.\"", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Marjorie Clifton"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121025pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 312, "question": "I'm doing your job for you, but what do you want to say to that?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "PRP", ",", "CC", "WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "TO", "VB", "TO", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 313, "answer": "I think there's another important thing.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121025pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 322, "question": "Can we have a -- can we have the same conversation that America's women are having across the country?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", ":", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "POS", "NNS", "VBP", "VBG", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 323, "answer": "Wait a minute.", "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["America"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121025pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 385, "question": "Are you falling for it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBG", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 386, "answer": "Well, it is a problem on the flip-flopping.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121025pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 443, "question": "John, how are you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 444, "answer": "I'm well.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121025pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "VBG", "RB", "TO", "."], "qSentId": 446, "question": "Were you listening to those three feisty ladies going at it just now?", "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "PRP", "VBG", "TO", "DT", "CD", "NN", "NNS", "VBG", "IN", "PRP", "RB", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 447, "answer": "I was trying not to.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121025pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "NN", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "JJ", "NNS", "VBP", "IN", "NN", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 457, "question": "What is your reading of it all?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 458, "answer": "Well, look, I think last time I was on your program, I said presidential campaigns are like basketball games.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121025pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "DT", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 474, "question": "Would you accept that charge?", "question_pos_tagged": ["MD", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 475, "answer": "Yeah, no, I don't.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121025pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 492, "question": "And then you have somebody like Richard Mourdock, who wants to be a senator, coming out and saying basically it's God's intent when women are impregnated by rapists, you must groan, don't you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "RB", "PRP", "VB", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "WP", "NNS", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", ",", "VBG", "RP", "CC", "VBG", "RB", "PRP", "VBZ", "NNP", "POS", "NN", "WRB", "NNS", "VBP", "VBN", "IN", "NNS", ",", "PRP", "MD", "VB", ",", "VB", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 493, "answer": "I do.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Richard Mourdock"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121025pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "JJ", "WRB", "JJ", "IN", "VBZ", "."], "qSentId": 504, "question": "Is it time he left the party, do you think?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "PRP", "RB", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 505, "answer": "I'm not sure how important that is.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Colin"], "LOCATION": ["United States"]}, "docId": "121025pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "JJ", "NN", "WDT", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "IN", "VBG", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NNPS", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "NNP", "IN", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 508, "question": "What reason would that be?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "NN", "MD", "IN", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 509, "answer": "Well, I think when you have somebody of your own race that you are proud of being president of the United States, I applaud Colin for standing with him.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121025pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP$", "NN", "RB", "VBD", "EX", "VBZ", "RB", "CD", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 524, "question": "Are you pleased to see your offspring being so active in this area?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBD", "TO", "VB", "PRP$", "NN", "VBG", "RB", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 525, "answer": "My dad always said there's only two things in the middle of the road.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["America"]}, "docId": "121025pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP$", "NN", "VBZ", "IN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "NNP", "POS", "VBG", "RP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 530, "question": "What is your view of where the country is?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "WRB", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "."], "aSentId": 531, "answer": "My view is that, you know, America's coming out of a deep hole.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121025pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 539, "question": "You would vote for him again?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 540, "answer": "I'm going to vote for him again.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121025pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 571, "question": "Dedicating it to Mitt Romney?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBG", "PRP", "TO", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 572, "answer": "I guess I am.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Mitt Romney"]}}]